All right, let's get into it. I'm a proud Jewish man, unapologetically Jewish, love being Jewish,
and I don't stand with Israel. You know, more than one thing can be true at the same time.
I absolutely unequivocally condemn Hamas and their actions against innocent Israelis. I also
unequivocally condemn the Israeli government and their decades-long oppression of Palestinian
people. If you have any humanity, you can't support the state of Israel and their actions
against Palestinians. Unless A, you just don't believe, you just don't know what's going on,
or B, you view Palestinians as less than human. And there has been a successfully collective
effort on the part of Western media to dehumanize Palestinians, calling everything they do
terror and everything Israel does, defense. Israel has the right to defend itself. We hear this over
and over again. Hamas started it. This was an unprovoked attack, unprovoked. Israel has had their
foot on the necks of Palestinians now for decades. They live in what amounts to an open-air prison.
Israel regularly cuts off water. Now they've cut off food supplies and electricity from these people.
This can be viewed as an act of genocide. And dehumanizing a people to justify the horrific
conditions in which you are forcing them to live is a Nazi tactic. And I as a Jew will never support
Nazi tactics. So I don't support the state of Israel. I support Israelis. And I don't support Hamas.
I support Palestinians. And I know Palestinians. And I know Israelis. And the thing they all have in
comment is that they want to live in peace. None of them want to live in fear. They all want to have
the opportunity to pursue life and happiness. So if you think you're supporting Jewish people by
posting the Israeli flag and standing with Israel, please recognize that you are standing on the side
of the oppressor. And I am pretty confident that history will show you are on the wrong side of
history in that regard.